Guide to the Capitol Hill Restoration Society records, 1904-2012 MS2009
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Leukhardt family papers, 1900-1995; MS2009 Series 9; 0.5 Linear feet
  - Family papers: Telephone Directory, 1904 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - House history: Article -- The American Home -- Curley Boswell's Restoration 1964, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - House history: Building Permits, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - House history: Purchase Contracts, Preservation Grant Project (1), undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - House history: Purchase History (2), undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - House history: Wallpaper sample front basement room, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - National Capital Centennial 1900: Program, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Old Marine Hospital, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Southeast Citizens Association: By-Laws, Constitution, Minutes, 1944-1950 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Southeast Citizens Association: House Tour, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Southeast Citizens Association: Membership, undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Washington Housing Association, 1949-1952 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Gregory New papers, 1964-1981; MS2009 Series 10; 10 Linear feet
  This series contains organizational records, meeting documentation, correspondence, brochure, by-laws, contracts, and testimony. This material dates from 1964-81. As with the Peter Glickert series, this series is an example of the personal papers of a very active citizen. This series has material for many neighborhood organizations that Mr. New worked with including the Capitol East Coalition for Housing, the Capitol East Community Crime Council, the Capitol Hill Community Council, the H. St. Project Area Committee, the Near Northeast Community Improvement Corporation, and the Public Interest Civic Association of Northeast Washington.
  - American Civil Liberties Union -- Capitol East Chapter, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Annual house and garden tours (11th, 14th, 22nd, 23rd, and 51st), 1980 May 11 - 2008 May 10-11; Series 10 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Assembly for a Better Community, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Bethune State, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Boys Club -- Eastern Branch, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Brent Elementary School -- Library, PTA, Citizens, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - C Street Tenants Association -- 1800 Block, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Campaign posters, 1974-1978; Series 10 (Map-folder 1, Flat box 145, Oversize-folder 1)
  - Campaign -- Ward 6 Candidates, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - 1968 Campaign -- Ward 6 Forums, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - 1969 Campaign -- Ward 6, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - 1971 Campaign -- Ward 6 Candidates, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - 1971 Campaign -- ward 6 Selection Committee, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - 1974 Campaign -- Ward 6, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - 1975 Campaign, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - 1978 Campaign, undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - 1979 Campaign, undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - The Capitol's Backyard a citizen's survey of recreation problems and possibilities in Capitol East, 1965 October 31; Series 10 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Children's Museum, 1977-1982 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Capitol Hill Directories, 1968-1969; Series 10 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Hill East, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing -- Budget, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing -- By-Laws, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing -- The Capitol East Communicator, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing -- Community Conference April, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing -- Community Conference July, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing -- Contract, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing -- History and Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing -- Meetings, 1976-1979 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing -- Membership and Elections, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing -- Neighborhood Improvement Program, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing -- Personnel, 1977-1979 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Capitol East Coalition for Housing -- Work Program, 1977-1980 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Capitol East Community Crime Council, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Capitol East Community Organizations, 1968-1975 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Capitol East Community School Board Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Capitol East Foundation, 1967-1971 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Capitol East Housing Coalition, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Capitol East Housing Coalition, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Capitol East Housing Center, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Capitol East Leadership Council, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Capitol East Natatorium, 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Capitol East Voter Information League, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Capitol Hill -- Biographies and Personal Notes, 1965-1976 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Hill Businesses, 1964-1974 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Hill -- Churches, 1969-1975 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill - Congressional Offices, 1965-1977 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Hill -- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Hill -- Parking, 1975-1977 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Hill -- Preservation and Beautification, 1967-1974 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Capitol Hill Action Group, 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Capitol Hill Babysitting Coop, 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Capitol Hill Citizens for Better Education, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Book Drives, 1963-1965 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    General
    See also flat-box 145 oversize folder 2
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Charter, 1964-1970 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Community Caper, 1970-1974; Series 10 (Flat box 145, Oversize-folder 4)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Cultural Affairs, undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Education, 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Education, Correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Education, Meetings, 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Education, School Visits, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Executive Board and Officers, 1964-1974 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Federal Relations, 1964-1966 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Home Rule, 1965-1970 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- labor Day Caper, 1964-1968 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Meeting Documentation, 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Meeting Documentation, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Meeting Documentation, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Meeting Documentation, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Meeting Documentation, 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Meeting Documentation, 1972-1974 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Membership Publicity, 1969-1975 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Planning and Zoning, 1963-1972 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- posters, 1965; Series 10 (Flat box 145, Oversize-folder 2)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- presentation of school library at Ludlow Elementary School, 1965 April 29; Series 10 (Box 144, Folder 7, Reel 1)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- President, 1965-1966 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Programs and Projects, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Recreation, 1964-1968 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Recreation/ERC Relations, 1966-1968 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Social Affairs, 1964-1973 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Social Welfare, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Testimony, 1964-1971 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Capitol Hill Community Council -- Washington Post Dealership, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Capitol Hill Citizens for Peace, 1967-1969 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Capitol Hill Group Ministry, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Capitol Hill Hospital, 1971-1975 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Capitol Hill Hospital, 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Capitol Hill Hospital, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Capitol Hill Hospital -- Community Relations, 1974-1981 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Capitol Hill Montessori School, 1964-1978 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Hill News -- Accounts, 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Hill News -- Ad Publicity, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill News -- Ad Rates, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Hill News -- Advertisers, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Hill News -- Business Correspondence and Contracts, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Hill News -- Contributions, 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Capitol Hill News -- Editorship, 1961-1969 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Capitol Hill News -- Incorporation, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Capitol Hill News -- Mailing and Volunteers, 1965-1967 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Capitol Hill News -- Management, 1965-1968 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Capitol Hill NOW, 1966-1974 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Capitol Hill Preservation Society, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Hill Prospects, 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society, 1965-1981 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society -- House and Garden Tour, 1966-1980 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society -- Newsletters, 1965-1971 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society -- Newsletters, 1972-1977 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society -- Newsletters, 1978-1993 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society -- Yost House, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Capitol Hill Southeast Citizens Association, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Capitol Hill Spectator Contributions, 1968 September-December (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Capitol Hill Spectator Contributions, 1969 January-May (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Capitol Hill Spectator Contributions, 1969 June-November (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Car barns, 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Charter Committee -- City, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Charter Committee -- Ward 6, Lists, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Charter Committee -- Ward 6, Meetings, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Charter Committee -- News and Information, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Charter Committee -- Publications, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Christ Child House, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Circle on the Hill, 1963-1966 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Circle on the Hill -- Market Day, 1963-1967 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Commissioner's Youth Council -- Area N Board, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Commissioner's Youth Council -- Area P Board, 1964-1967 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - community activism posters, 1968-1974; Series 10 (Flat box 145, Oversize-folder 3)
  - Community Corporation of the Northeast, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Community Directory of Friendship House Settlement neighborhood development program operation and affiliate programs, 1967 August; Series 10 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Concerned Neighbors of Capitol Hill, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Congressional Cemetery, 1976-1981 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Credit Unions -- Capitol East, 1965-1980 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Crime Prevention Day, 1971 February (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Crime Stoppers, 1968-1979 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - DC Bicentennial Assembly, 1972-1975 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - DC Bicentennial Assembly -- Area 5 Delegation, 1972-1975 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - DC Board of Education -- Kane, 1977-1981 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - DC Board of Education -- Rieffel, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - DC Budget Testimony, 1965-1967 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - DC Council -- Winter and Urban Homesteading, 1973-1980 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - DC Home Rule Hearing --, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - DC Housing and Community Development -- Area 5, 1974-1977 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - DC Metro Police -- 1st District, 1976-1979 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - DC Metro Police -- 5th District, 1964-1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Eastern Market -- Fire House, 1964-1979 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Education -- Ward 6, 1959-1974 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Education -- Ward 5, Principles, 1971-1974 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Education -- Ward 6, Warren, 1970-1979 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Eleven hundred Block, East Capitol St NE, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Emergency Recreation Council, 1964-1967 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Emergency Recreation Council -- Lists, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Emergency Recreation Council -- Survey, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Experiment in International Living, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Federal City College, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Federally Assisted Code Enforcement, 1964-1972 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Finishing Touches a collection of recipes for finishing wood, 1963; Series 10 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    Published by the Circle-on-the-Hill for the benefit of Friendship House
  - Folger Library, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Friendship House, 1962-1981 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Friendship House -- NAC, 1974-1976 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Friendship House -- NDP Advisory Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Friendship House -- Newsletter and Fact Sheet, 1963-1978 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - H St NE Business Organizations, 1969-1977 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Hechinger Plaza, 1978-1980 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Hine Expansion -- Brochure, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Hine Expansion -- Community Council Correspondence, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Hine Expansion -- Community Council papers, 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Hine Expansion -- Personal Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Hine Expansion -- Statements of Others, 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Hospitality House, 1969-1979 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Housing -- Capitol East, 1964-1977 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Housing Company, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Attendance, 1971-1978 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Budget and Funding, 1971-1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Businessmen, 1970-1974 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Bylaws, 1970-1979 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Calendars, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Committees, 1971-1980 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Community Development 4, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Community Development 5, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Community Involvement, 1970-1975 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Conflict of Interest, 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Contract and Negotiations, 1970-1972 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Contract and Negotiations, 1973-1975 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Credentials Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Economic Development Studies, 1975-1980 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Elections and Rosters, 1970-1979 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Evaluation, Chang, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Hearing on Renewal, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Housing, 1971-1980 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Incorporation, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Interim Use, 1970-1974 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Meetings, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Meetings, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - H St. Project Area Committee Meetings (1), 1972 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - H St. Project Area Committee Meetings (2), 1972 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - H St. Project Area Committee -- Meetings, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Meetings, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Meetings, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Meetings, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Meetings, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Meetings, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Meetings, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Meetings, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Meetings, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- NDP 1, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- NDP 3, 1970-1971 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- NDP 4, 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- NDP 5, 1974-1978 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- News Reports, 1970-1980 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Newsletter, 1970-1980 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Nominating, 1970-1974 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Parcels and Delays, 1973-1976 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Personnel, 1970-1980 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Pictures, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Planning, 1971-1980 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Property and Office, 1970-1973 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Proposals from Community Groups, 1971-1978 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Publicity Committee, 1971-1976 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Recognition and History, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Rehabilitation, 1970-1974 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Relations to Other Agencies, 1972-1978 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Status Reports, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Training, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - H St Project Area Committee -- Transport, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - H Street Urban Renewal Area, 1970 June 25 - 1971 May; Series 10 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Independent Living for the Handicapped, undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Ingram memorial Church, 1964-1969 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Keller Lutheran Church, 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Kingman Lake Recreation, 1968-1974 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Kiwanis, 1966-1975 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - League for Universal justice, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Lincoln Park Area, 1969-1981 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Logan School, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Lovejoy -- Edmonds School Replacement, 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Mary Dickerson Scholarship, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Metro -- Capitol East Studies, 1965-1979 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Model Cities, 1968-1969 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Model Cities, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Model Cities, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Model Cities, 1972-1974 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Modern Strivers and eastern HS Freedom School, 1967-1970 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Museum of African Art, 1971-1977 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - National Children's Island, 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Near Northeast, 1967-1980 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Near Northeast Community Improvement Corporation (NNE-CIC) -- Alcoholism, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - NNE-CIC -- Board Elections, 1968-1978 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - NNE-CIC -- Board Elections/Candidates, 1969-1971 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - NNE-CIC -- Board Meetings, 1967-1969 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - NNE-CIC -- Board Meetings, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - NNE-CIC -- Board Meetings, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - NNE-CIC -- Board Meetings, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - NNE-CIC -- By-Laws, 1965-1971 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - NNE-CIC -- Committees, 1969-1972 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - NNE-CIC -- Community Advisory Council, 1967-1969 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - NNE-CIC -- Creation, 1965-1966 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - NNE-CIC -- Finance, 1968-1974 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - NNE-CIC -- Food Coop Proposal, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - NNE-CIC -- H St Proposals, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - NNE-CIC -- King programs and proposals, 1970-1974 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - NNE-CIC -- Members, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - NNE-CIC -- Mountain Tip Newsletters, 1968-1971 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - NNE-CIC -- NAC Meeting, 1969-1972 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - NNE-CIC -- Programs and Activities, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - NNE-CIC -- Programs and Activities, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - NNE-CIC -- Programs and Activities, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - NNE-CIC -- Programs and Activities, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - NNE-CIC -- Programs and Activities, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - NNE-CIC -- Reports, 1969-1980 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - NNE-CIC -- Board Rosters, 1969-1971 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - NNE-CIC -- Staff and Reorganization, 1968-1971 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - NNE-CIC -- Workshops, 1969-1980 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - NNE-CIC -- Youth members, 1969-1971 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Near Northeast Federation, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Near Northeast Interagency Council, 1970-1973 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Near Northeast Renewal, 1969-1978 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Neighborhood Arts Council -- Area 5, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Neighborhood Planning Council, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Neighborhood Planning Council -- Area 15, Constitution, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Neighborhood Planning Council -- Area 15, meeting, 1967-1970 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Neighborhood Planning Council -- Area 15, Programs, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Neighborhood Planning Council -- Area 16, 1967-1977 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Northeast Reconstruction Organization, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - People -- Capitol Hill, 1968-1978 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Potomac Avenue High Rise, 1971-1974 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Proposal to plan for a model neighborhood a summary for citizen considered, 1968 March; Series 10 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Public Interest Civic Association of Northeast Washington (PICA of NE), 1968-1981 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - PICA of NE -- Birthdays and Deaths, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - PICA of NE -- Constitution, 1972-1976 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - PICA of NE -- Farmers Market, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - PICA of NE -- Federal Relations, 1971-1981 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - PICA of NE -- Finance, 1970-1981 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - PICA of NE -- Finley's Gym, 1974-1976 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - PICA of NE -- Fundraising, 1971-1977 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - PICA of NE -- Juniors, 1974-1976 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - PICA of NE -- Meeting, 1965-1970 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - PICA of NE -- Meeting, 1971-1973 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - PICA of NE -- Meeting, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - PICA of NE -- Meeting, 1976-1980 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - PICA of NE -- Meeting, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - PICA of NE -- Membership, 1970-1979 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - PICA of NE -- Newsletter, 1976-1981 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - PICA of NE -- Newsletter editing, 1977-1981 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - PICA of NE -- Officers and Delegates, 1969-1981 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - PICA of NE -- Presidency, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - PICA of NE -- Zoning, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Recreation in Capitol Hill, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Recreation Testimony, 1964-1965 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Republicans in Ward 6, 1964-1976 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Saint Marks, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Saturdays at the Ball Game, 1966-1971 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - School Action Council -- Committee on Community Action on Public Education, 1966-1967 (Box 53, Folder 10)